Guide to the Cornell Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender Coalition records, 1967-1999
Cornell Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender Coalition records, 1967-1999
- Series IV. Subject Files
  - Cornell University Information
    - Bylaws of Cornell University, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - CRESP (Center for Religion, Ethics, and Social Policy) publications, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Campus council, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Campus governance, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Charter of Cornell University, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Clippings: Cornell student papers, 1966-1992 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Cornell Political Forum, March 1989, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Cornell Reports, Winter 1983, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Harassment (official), 1980-1984 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Latin America: Study Group on Lesbians and Gay in Latin America, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 85)
    - Maps of Cornell University (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Minority and disadvantaged students, 1970-1973 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Organization and Event-Planning Handbook, Cornell University, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Policy Notebook for Students, Faculty and Staff, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - Policy Notebook for Students, Faculty and Staff, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - Policy Notebook for Students, Faculty and Staff Addenda, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 91)
    - Students and Title IX (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Theories of Personality: first preliminary examination for Psychology/Sociology 385, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Cuomo, Mario (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Demonstrations, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - "Example of bad logic" (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Film, 1981-1995 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Gittings, Barbara, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - HIV testing, 1985-1990 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Health: AIDS Instructional Guide, Grades K-12, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Health: Supplement to AIDS Instructional Guide, Grades K-12, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Human Life Amendments (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Immigration, 1983-1990 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Intravenous drug users, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Issues: produced materials, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Kids, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Legislation: publications by New York State, 1973-1981 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Legislation (mostly mailings from organizations that work on gay and lesbian legislation), 1977-1992 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
  - Lesbian and Gay Awareness week, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Lesbians, Gays, Bisexuals of color, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Medical Doctors, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - March on Albany, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Marino, Ralph, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Memorial, Alan Evan Cherry, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - Military discrimination, 1991-1999 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - National March on Washington for Lesbian and Gay Rights, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Nondiscrimination policy relating to sexual orientation, State University of New York, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 23a)
  - Northeast Lesbian/Gay Student Activist Conference, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 23b)
  - Ohrenstein, Manfred, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Organizations
    - AIDS Task Force of Central New York, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - BACADI Labor Committee (Bay Area Committee Against the Briggs Initiative) (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Bates College, Gay-Straight Alliance, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Binghamton University, Harpur Gay Alliance, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Boston University, Gay People of B.U., 1981 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Broome County Gay Alliance, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Bryn Mawr College (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - CACHR (Capital Area Coalition for Human Rights), 1977 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - CDGPC (Capital District Gay Political Caucus), 1981 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - CUGALA (Cornell University Gay and Lesbian Alumni Association), 1980 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - California Outreach Group (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Colgate University, Lesbian and Gay Student Alliance, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Couples, Inc.: The National Organization for Family Diversity, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - GMHC (Gay Men's Health Crisis) (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Gay Alliance of Genessee Valley, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Gay and Lesbian Advocates and Defenders, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Gay Light Collective, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Gay Rights National Lobby, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - "Hordes of Womyn" (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Human Rights Campaign Fund (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Hunter College, Gay Academic Union, 1974-1982 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Ivy League Student Groups, 1969-1989 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - LAGPONY (Lesbian and Gay People of New York State), 1980 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Lambda Alliance at Rensselaer (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Llego: The Latina/o Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender Organization, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - MGPC (Massachusetts Gay Political Caucus), 1981 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Mansfield Commonwealth Association of Students, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - NGLTF (National Gay and Lesbian Task Force), 1988-1992 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - NYSCGO (New York State Coalition of Gay Organizations), 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - New York State Lesbian and Gay Lobby, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - New York University, Gay People's Union, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - New York University School of Law and Rutgers University Law, Lesbian and Gay Law Students, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Partnership (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Peoples College of Law of the National Lawyers Guild, 1975? (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Renaissance House (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Rochester Gay Task Force, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - San Francisco Fund Raising Committee for the Gay March for Human Rights, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Stanford University, Gay and Lesbian Alliance, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - State University of New York - Albany, Gay and Lesbian Alliance, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - State University of New York - Oswego, Gay and Lesbian Alliance (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Syracuse University, Gay Students Association, 1976-1985 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - University of California - Berkeley, Gay and Lesbian Union, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - University of Delaware Gay and Student Union, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - University of Massachusetts - Amherst, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - University of Vermont, Gay Student Union, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Viewpoint: Speakers for Radical Change, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Outwrite! Third National Lesbian and Gay Writers Conference, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Pamphlet on New Law Lobby, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Pamphlets: safer sex, HIV (Box 10, Folder 81-82)
  - Prisons, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Prisons: articles, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Programs, 1980-1990 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Psychiatry, 1973-1977 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Rape information (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Religion, 1977-1993 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Research, 1985-1990 (Box 11, Folder 34-35)
  - Resource Guide on Homophobia, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Scondras, David, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Seward, James, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Sodomy law (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Speak Out, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Stonewall Gay Games, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - "Struggle against sexual oppression" (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Syracuse gay activities, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Transgender issues (Box 11, Folder 54)
- Series V. Newsletters, Publications, and Other Literature
  - Photocopied Books and Journals, 1972-1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Publications and Newsletters, 1985-1992 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Publications and Newsletters from Tompkins County, NY, 1985-1992 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Informational Booklets and Single-Sheet Publications, 1986-1992 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Film Publications, 1988-1991 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Pamphlets and Small Publications, 1988-1992 (Box 13, Folder 10)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
The following materials have been cataloged separately and may be found using the online library catalog.
ACT UP Reports: a Newsletter of ACT UP New York (1989)
AIDS Treatment News (1989)
The Alyson Lesbian Book Catalog (1988-1990)
Ambiphysct (1992)
The American Gay Atheist/ The American Gay and Lesbian Atheist (1989-1991)
Amethyst (1991-1992)
Anti-Gay Legislation: An Attempt to Sanction Inequality? Report of the Litigation Project on Anti-Gay Legislation (1982)
Asian/Pacific Lesbians and Gays, Inc. Newsletter (1987)
Athena: Newsletter of the Cornell Women’s Center (1987)
Bi Women: the Newsletter of the Boston Bisexual Women’s Network (1988-1993)
The Bridge (1989)
The Center Voice: the Lesbian and Gay Services Center Newsletter (1990-1992)
The Connection (1987-1992)
Cornell Reproductive Rights Alliance Newsletter (1990)
Gay Fathers Forum Newsletter (1989)
The Gay Iowan (1986)
Gaylactic Gazette (1989)
Gayspace: Newsletter of the Gay Peoples Union (1986)
G.L.A.D. Briefs: a newsletter from Gay and Lesbian Advocates and Defenders (1988-1992)
The Goodstein Report on Citizen Activism in America (no date)
G.U.L.F. Gayzette (1987-1992)
The Haworth Press: New Books and Journals in Human Sexuality (1990)
HEAL: Health – Education – AIDS Liaison (1990)
Hera (1988-1992) Herizon Newsletter (1987-1990)
The Intercollegiate: from the Boston Intercollegiate Lesbian and Gay Alliance (1986-1989)
International Gay Men’s News (1992)
Issues: A Quarterly Publication of AIDS Project Los Angeles (1987)
The James White Review: A Gay Men’s Literary Quarterly (1990)
Ladyslipper Catalog and Resource Guide: Recordings by Women (1991-1992)
Lambda Rising News (1990-1991)
Lambda Update/ Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, Inc. (1986-1990)
The Lavender Line: the Newsletter from Heritage of Pride, Inc. (1992)
MACT: Men of All Colors Together (1987-1988)
Men’s Work: a newsletter for the Ithaca Men’s Network (1987)
Nashville Lambda Communications Guide (1991)
National Center for Lesbian Rights Newsletter (1992)
N.E.L.G.S.U. Newsletter (1989)
News from LGAP: Lesbians and Gays at Penn (1988)
NOGLSTP: National Organization of Gay and Lesbian Scientists and Technical Professionals Newsletter (1989)
North Bi Northwest: The Newsletter of the Seattle Bisexual Women’s Network (1990)
On Liberty: The Newspaper of the Cornell Civil Liberties Union (1990)
Our Voice/Pride Institute (1987-1991)
Outlines (1985-1992)
Positively Aware: The Monthly Journal of Test Positive Aware Network (1992)
Produce Report (1990)
Q-Press: The Queer Camera (1992)
San Francisco International Lesbian and Gay Film Festival (1987-1991)
Sappho’s Isle: The Tri-State Lesbian newspaper (1992)
Sin Fronteras: A Gay Latino Journal (1984)
South End Press: New Titles and Backlist (1990)
Speak Out: a Newsletter from the International Gay and Lesbian Youth Organization (1988-1989)
States of Mind: the Publication of the Mental Health Association in Tompkins County (1990-1992)
Stop the Violence: the Newsletter of the New York City Gay and Lesbian Anti-Violence Project (1990)
Talisman Magazine: Hunter College (1986)
Task Force Report: a Newsletter of the National Gay and Lesbian Task Force (1985-1992)
Tompkins County Task Force for Battered Women: Newsletter (1991)
Upstate Gay Student Groups Newsletter (1988)
Wild Women Sports (1992)
Women’s Info News (1987-1992)